[
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f95136a",
    "correctAnswer": "Collage",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Watercolor",
      "Sculpture",
      "Pointilism"
    ],
    "question": "What is the word for a composition made of cut and pasted pieces of materials?",
    "tags": [
      "art",
      "words",
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950ea7",
    "correctAnswer": "J. K. Rowling",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Christopher Tolkien",
      "Philip Pullman",
      "C. S. Lewis"
    ],
    "question": "Which author wrote 'Quidditch Through the Ages'?",
    "tags": [
      "literature",
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f9513b2",
    "correctAnswer": "The Hobbit",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Charlotte's Web",
      "Alice's Adventures in Wonderland",
      "Bluebeard"
    ],
    "question": "In which book does 'Bilbo Baggins' appear?",
    "tags": [
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950ebe",
    "correctAnswer": "J. K. Rowling",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Christopher Tolkien",
      "Philip Pullman",
      "C. S. Lewis"
    ],
    "question": "Which author wrote 'Harry Potter'?",
    "tags": [
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950e37",
    "correctAnswer": "George Orwell",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Joseph Conrad",
      "Virginia Woolf",
      "Charles Dickens"
    ],
    "question": "Which author wrote 'Animal Farm'?",
    "tags": [
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f9c",
    "correctAnswer": "William Shakespeare",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Arthur C. Clarke",
      "Isaac Newton",
      "Enid Blyton"
    ],
    "question": "Which author wrote 'Hamlet'?",
    "tags": [
      "literature",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950eab",
    "correctAnswer": "J. K. Rowling",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Christopher Tolkien",
      "Philip Pullman",
      "C. S. Lewis"
    ],
    "question": "Which author wrote 'Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix'?",
    "tags": [
      "harry_potter",
      "literature",
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950167",
    "correctAnswer": "Charles Dickens",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Thomas Hardy",
      "James Joyce",
      "Emily BrontÃ«"
    ],
    "question": "Who wrote \"A Christmas Carol\"?",
    "tags": [
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951367",
    "correctAnswer": "A Palette",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "An eisel",
      "A square",
      "A pitcher"
    ],
    "question": "What is the word given to a flat board used by a painter to mix and hold colors?",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "art",
      "painting",
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f95139b",
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires",
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians",
      "Twilight"
    ],
    "question": "In which book series does 'Ginny Weasley' appear?",
    "tags": [
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f3a",
    "correctAnswer": "J. R. R. Tolkien",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "G. K. Chesterton",
      "Philip Pullman",
      "C. S. Lewis"
    ],
    "question": "Which author wrote 'The History of Middle-earth'?",
    "tags": [
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950230",
    "correctAnswer": "Andy Warhol ",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jackson Pollock",
      "Gertrude Stein",
      "Aaron Copland"
    ],
    "question": "Who is the American artist who uses Campbell's Soup cans in his pop art?",
    "tags": [],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9501a8",
    "correctAnswer": "The Chronicles of Narnia",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires",
      "Harry Potter",
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians"
    ],
    "question": "In which book series does 'Prince Caspian' appear?",
    "tags": [
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950169",
    "correctAnswer": "Romeo",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Juliet",
      "Hamlet",
      "Paris"
    ],
    "question": "Who said 'But, soft! what light through yonder window breaks'?",
    "tags": [
      "theater"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950eac",
    "correctAnswer": "J. K. Rowling",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Christopher Tolkien",
      "Philip Pullman",
      "C. S. Lewis"
    ],
    "question": "Which author wrote 'The Tales of Beedle the Bard'?",
    "tags": [
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9501a9",
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires",
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians",
      "Twilight"
    ],
    "question": "In which book series does 'Neville Longbottom' appear?",
    "tags": [
      "fictitious_characters",
      "literature",
      "young_adult",
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f95139e",
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires",
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians",
      "Twilight"
    ],
    "question": "In which book series does 'Severus Snape' appear?",
    "tags": [
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f9513d9",
    "correctAnswer": "The Hunger Games",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires",
      "Harry Potter",
      "Mortal Engines Quartet"
    ],
    "question": "In which book series does 'Katniss Everdeen' appear?",
    "tags": [
      "young_adult",
      "literature",
      "fictitious_characters",
      "general_knowledge",
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950eb0",
    "correctAnswer": "J. K. Rowling",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Christopher Tolkien",
      "Philip Pullman",
      "C. S. Lewis"
    ],
    "question": "Which author wrote 'Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows'?",
    "tags": [
      "literature",
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950161",
    "correctAnswer": "J.R.R. Tolkien",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Roald Dahl",
      "George R.R. Martin",
      "Brandon Sanderson"
    ],
    "question": "Who wrote \"The Hobbit\"?",
    "tags": [
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "625740939da29df7b05f73e8",
    "correctAnswer": "A paleontologist is tasked with protecting two children when cloned dinosaurs are set free.",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "During WWII a Jewish waiter uses humor to protect his son from the realities of war.",
      "A maverick teacher emboldens his students to new heights of self-expression.",
      "A car salesman's inept crime falls apart due to his and his henchmen's bungling."
    ],
    "question": "What is the plot of the movie Jurassic Park?",
    "tags": [
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fc31",
    "correctAnswer": "\"It's alive! It's alive!\"",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "\"Stella! Hey, Stella!\"",
      "\"My precious...\"",
      "\"I'm walkin' here!\""
    ],
    "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Frankenstein'?",
    "tags": [
      "quotes",
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fc2d",
    "correctAnswer": "\"You're gonna need a bigger boat.\"",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "\"A census taker once tried to test me. I ate his liver with some fava beans and a nice Chianti.\"",
      "\"Wait a minute, wait a minute. You ain't heard nothin' yet!\"",
      "\"Mother of mercy, is this the end of Rico?\""
    ],
    "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Jaws'?",
    "tags": [
      "quotes",
      "film",
      "general_knowledge",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f8bb",
    "correctAnswer": "Harrison Ford",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Marlon Brando",
      "Samuel L. Jackson",
      "Al Pacino"
    ],
    "question": "Which actor played the role of Indiana Jones in Raiders of the Lost Ark?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "acting",
      "general_knowledge",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc4b",
    "correctAnswer": "\"I'm gonna make him an offer he can't refuse.\"",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "\"I love the smell of napalm in the morning.\"",
      "\"I have nipples Greg. Could you milk me?\"",
      "\"Elementary, my dear Watson.\""
    ],
    "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'The Godfather'?",
    "tags": [
      "quotes",
      "film",
      "general_knowledge",
      "cult_films",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "62573efd9da29df7b05f7380",
    "correctAnswer": "A man becomes concerned for his Jewish workforce after witnessing their persecution by the Nazis.",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "In order to power the city, beasts have to scare children so that they scream.",
      "A girl wanders into a world ruled by gods, witches, and spirits, where humans are changed into beasts.",
      "King Arthur and his Knights embark on a search for a religious relic."
    ],
    "question": "What is the plot of the movie Schindler's List?",
    "tags": [
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fbeb",
    "correctAnswer": "\"I have had it with these motherââ snakes on this motherââ plane!\"",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "\"Not my tempo.\"",
      "\"Oh, Jerry, don't let's ask for the moon. We have the stars.\"",
      "\"Tell 'em to go out there with all they got and win just one for the Gipper.\""
    ],
    "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Snakes on a Plane'?",
    "tags": [
      "quotes",
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9507c7",
    "correctAnswer": "Harrison Ford",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mark Hamill",
      "Brad Pitt",
      "Pedro Pascal"
    ],
    "question": "Which actor originally played the role of Han Solo in Star Wars?",
    "tags": [
      "star_wars",
      "film",
      "acting",
      "general_knowledge",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9501f0",
    "correctAnswer": "Christopher Nolan",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg",
      "Woody Allen",
      "Martin Scorsese"
    ],
    "question": "Which director directed Interstellar?",
    "tags": [
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "625698689da29df7b05f7285",
    "correctAnswer": "Captain America",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Thor",
      "The Collector",
      "Spiderman"
    ],
    "question": "Chris Evans plays the role of which character in the Marvel Cinematic Unvierse?",
    "tags": [
      "mcu",
      "film",
      "acting",
      "marvel",
      "comics",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "625741333d2f5c16bfb88345",
    "correctAnswer": "A human soldier is sent from 2029 to 1984 to stop an almost indestructible cyborg killing machine.",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Marine observes the effects of war on his fellow recruits from their boot camp training to fighting in a war.",
      "The lives of mob hitmen, a boxer, a gangster and his wife, and a pair of bandits intertwine in four tales.",
      "Historical events unfold from the perspective of an Alabama man with an IQ of 75."
    ],
    "question": "What is the plot of the movie The Terminator?",
    "tags": [
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f947",
    "correctAnswer": "Pirates of the Caribbean",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Godfather",
      "The Silence of the Lambs",
      "The Birds"
    ],
    "question": "Which film contains the character 'Captain Jack Sparrow'?",
    "tags": [
      "fictitious_characters",
      "film",
      "general_knowledge",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "62573fee9da29df7b05f73b7",
    "correctAnswer": "Toy Story",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pan's Labyrinth",
      "The Exorcist",
      "Gandhi"
    ],
    "question": "Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'A cowboy doll is threatened when a new spaceman figure supplants him as top toy.'",
    "tags": [
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "625741159da29df7b05f740b",
    "correctAnswer": "A prince cursed to spend his days as a monster sets out to regain his humanity.",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A paleontologist is tasked with protecting two children when cloned dinosaurs are set free.",
      "The son of a former boxer is trained by his father for a mixed martial arts tournament.",
      "A young F.B.I. cadet must receive the help of a cannibal to help catch another serial killer."
    ],
    "question": "What is the plot of the movie Beauty and the Beast?",
    "tags": [
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f914",
    "correctAnswer": "The Silence of the Lambs",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Casablanca",
      "A Nightmare on Elm Street",
      "Taxi Driver"
    ],
    "question": "Which film contains the character 'Hannibal Lecter'?",
    "tags": [
      "acting",
      "film",
      "horror",
      "general_knowledge",
      "fictitious_characters",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fc0f",
    "correctAnswer": "\"Take your stinking paws off me, you damned dirty ape.\"",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "\"Mrs. Robinson, you're trying to seduce me. Aren't you?\"",
      "\"Toga! Toga!\"",
      "\"Attica! Attica!\""
    ],
    "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Planet of the Apes'?",
    "tags": [
      "quotes",
      "film",
      "general_knowledge",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "624dba55cd90beeca353156c",
    "correctAnswer": "Daniel Craig",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sean Connery",
      "Roger Moore",
      "Timothy Dalton"
    ],
    "question": "Who played the role of James Bond in Skyfall?",
    "tags": [
      "james_bond",
      "film",
      "acting",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "62573f899da29df7b05f73a1",
    "correctAnswer": "A young man joins forces with an old man, a cocky pilot, a beast and two robots to save the galaxy.",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The son of a city's mastermind falls in love with a working-class prophet.",
      "After two male musicians witness a murder, they flee in an all-female band disguised as women.",
      "Violence and mayhem ensue after a man stumbles upon more than two million dollars."
    ],
    "question": "What is the plot of the movie Star Wars?",
    "tags": [
      "film"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9507bb",
    "correctAnswer": "Clint Eastwood",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Matt Damon",
      "Robert De Niro",
      "Sean Connery"
    ],
    "question": "Which actor has featured in films including The Good, the Bad and the Ugly and Million Dollar Baby?",
    "tags": [
      "film",
      "acting",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fbdb",
    "correctAnswer": "\"This is the day you will always remember as the day you almost caught Captain Jack Sparrow!\"",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "\"My precious.\"",
      "\"I'll get you, my pretty, and your little dog, too!\"",
      "\"Keep your friends close, but your enemies closer.\""
    ],
    "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Pirates of the Caribbean: The Curse of the Black Pearl'?",
    "tags": [
      "quotes",
      "film",
      "general_knowledge",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "624c60dc50d1a5e051325a78",
    "correctAnswer": "Stamppot",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ropa Vieja",
      "Meat Pie",
      "Ramen"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these dishes is most associated with Netherlands?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "the_netherlands",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9502f6",
    "correctAnswer": "Bread ",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cheese",
      "Cake",
      "Wine"
    ],
    "question": "Bruschetta is what?",
    "tags": [
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950234",
    "correctAnswer": "Ronald Mcdonald",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The King",
      "Donald Burger",
      "Meato"
    ],
    "question": "Who is McDonald's mascot?",
    "tags": [
      "business",
      "advertising",
      "fictitious_characters",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95023e",
    "correctAnswer": "Haggis ",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Neeps and Tatties",
      "Pizza Crunch",
      "Cullen Skink"
    ],
    "question": "Which Scottish Dish Is Boiled In The Stomach Lining Of A Sheep?",
    "tags": [
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f951557",
    "correctAnswer": "Texas ",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Florida",
      "California",
      "Georgia"
    ],
    "question": "Which US state is most associated with Chilli Con Carne?",
    "tags": [
      "food_and_drink",
      "food",
      "us_states"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "627164241ba117625baac94a",
    "correctAnswer": "Scotland",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Italy",
      "Romania",
      "Mexico"
    ],
    "question": "Which country is associated with the drink whisky?",
    "tags": [
      "drink",
      "alcohol"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9502bc",
    "correctAnswer": "Pasta ",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Chicken",
      "Cheese",
      "Bread"
    ],
    "question": "What Is Ravioli? ",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "general_knowledge",
      "words",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f951555",
    "correctAnswer": "Samosa",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pakora",
      "Curry",
      "Bhaji"
    ],
    "question": "What name is given to an Indian deep fried triangular pastry?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "india",
      "pastry",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f95163b",
    "correctAnswer": "Green",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Blue",
      "Yellow",
      "Red"
    ],
    "question": " What colour is the flesh of an avocado?",
    "tags": [
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f951635",
    "correctAnswer": "Bread",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cheese",
      "Fruit",
      "Nut"
    ],
    "question": " What type of food is pitta?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "general_knowledge",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950214",
    "correctAnswer": "Roald Dahl ",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Charles Dickens",
      "Jacqueline Wilson",
      "Morgan Scott"
    ],
    "question": "Who wrote the book Charlie and the Chocolate Factory?",
    "tags": [
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95023f",
    "correctAnswer": "Al dente ",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tartilli",
      "Forte Benne",
      "Parpa Delle"
    ],
    "question": "Which Italian phrase is used to describe pasta cooked only until it offers a slight resistance when bitten?",
    "tags": [
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "624c60ad50d1a5e051325a6c",
    "correctAnswer": "Italy",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Equatorial Guinea",
      "Spain",
      "Austria"
    ],
    "question": "Where in the world would you most expect to be served Lasagna?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "general_knowledge",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950246",
    "correctAnswer": "Avocado ",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cucumber",
      "Tomato",
      "Mango"
    ],
    "question": "Which Is The Main Ingredient Of Guacamole?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "6271643d1ba117625baac951",
    "correctAnswer": "Ireland",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Romania",
      "Mongolia",
      "Finland"
    ],
    "question": "In which country is guinness a popular drink?",
    "tags": [
      "drink",
      "alcohol"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "624c60f550d1a5e051325a7f",
    "correctAnswer": "Scotland",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Estonia",
      "Hungary",
      "Thailand"
    ],
    "question": "Where in the world would you most expect to be served Haggis?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f95164a",
    "correctAnswer": "Lettuce",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Egg",
      "Tomato",
      "Bread"
    ],
    "question": " Iceberg, Boston, and Bibb are types of what?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "624c60c095b12387e142c79b",
    "correctAnswer": "Ramen",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ceviche",
      "Plov",
      "Chilli Crab"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these dishes would you most expect to find in Japan?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "624c6148badf21197f98f771",
    "correctAnswer": "United States",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brunei",
      "Bahrain",
      "Vietnam"
    ],
    "question": "Where in the world would you most expect to be served Mac 'N' Cheese?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f9515cc",
    "correctAnswer": "Spain ",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Italy",
      "France",
      "Russia"
    ],
    "question": "From which country does the dish paella originate?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "general_knowledge",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "6239f8019129041bf3925cbd",
    "correctAnswer": "Alpha",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Apple",
      "Animal",
      "Aeroplan"
    ],
    "question": "What word is used in the NATO Phonetic Alphabet for the letter A?",
    "tags": [
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951067",
    "correctAnswer": "Bonsai",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ornamental Shrubbery",
      "Decorage",
      "Topiary"
    ],
    "question": "What is the name given to the art of miniaturising trees and maintaining their small size?",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "6239f8099129041bf3925cc0",
    "correctAnswer": "Delta",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dog",
      "Danube",
      "Dig"
    ],
    "question": "What word is used in the NATO Phonetic Alphabet for the letter D?",
    "tags": [
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "6239f843a72e7a347ac879da",
    "correctAnswer": "Yankee",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Yearly",
      "Yum",
      "Yurt"
    ],
    "question": "What word is used in the NATO Phonetic Alphabet for the letter Y?",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "language",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f95045e",
    "correctAnswer": "5 Gold Rings",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "5 Drummers Drumming",
      "5 Swans a Swimming",
      "5 Lords a Leaping"
    ],
    "question": "What Did My True Love Give To Me On The \"Fifth\" Day Of Christmas\"?",
    "tags": [
      "christmas",
      "lyrics",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "6239f8049129041bf3925cbe",
    "correctAnswer": "Bravo",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Boot",
      "Ball",
      "Baby"
    ],
    "question": "What word is used in the NATO Phonetic Alphabet for the letter B?",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950fb3",
    "correctAnswer": "Apple",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Microsoft",
      "Google",
      "Linux"
    ],
    "question": "Who Make Macintosh Computers?",
    "tags": [
      "technology",
      "business",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950121",
    "correctAnswer": "Gold",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Invisible",
      "Dead",
      "Water"
    ],
    "question": "What does the \"touch of Midas\" turn everything?",
    "tags": [
      "mythology",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c3e7cc59eab6f95224a",
    "correctAnswer": "Narcissism",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Greed",
      "Ego",
      "Obsession"
    ],
    "question": "In the field of psychiatry, which term means self-love?",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "psychology"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951c69",
    "correctAnswer": "Five Gold Rings",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Five Lords a Leaping",
      "Five Drummers Drumming",
      "Five Calling Birds"
    ],
    "question": "According to the Christmas song what did my true love give to me on the fifth day of Christmas?",
    "tags": [
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951b87",
    "correctAnswer": "Apple",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Blackberry",
      "Microsoft",
      "Google"
    ],
    "question": "Which computer company was set up by Steven Jobs and Stephen Wozniak?",
    "tags": [
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950079",
    "correctAnswer": "Washington DC",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "New York City",
      "Brussels",
      "Geneva"
    ],
    "question": "Where is Capitol Hill?",
    "tags": [
      "places",
      "politics",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "6239f80b9129041bf3925cc1",
    "correctAnswer": "Echo",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Elton",
      "Elbow",
      "Enable"
    ],
    "question": "What word is used in the NATO Phonetic Alphabet for the letter E?",
    "tags": [
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9503f9",
    "correctAnswer": "Robots",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Aliens",
      "Gods",
      "Wizards"
    ],
    "question": "Transformers are ___________ in disguise. ",
    "tags": [
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "623b584dfd6c701a921183ae",
    "correctAnswer": "Russia",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Argentina",
      "Hungary",
      "Spain"
    ],
    "question": "In which country would you find The Kremlin and Red Square?",
    "tags": [
      "tourist_attractions",
      "general_knowledge",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "623b5801fd6c701a92118390",
    "correctAnswer": "USA",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Saudi Arabia",
      "Belgium",
      "France"
    ],
    "question": "In which country would you find Yosemite National Park?",
    "tags": [],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "623740bfcb85f7ce9e949d1e",
    "correctAnswer": "New Delhi",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kolkata",
      "Jaipur",
      "Mumbai"
    ],
    "question": "What is the capital city of India?",
    "tags": [
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "623742d4cb85f7ce9e949df5",
    "correctAnswer": "United States of America",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand",
      "Ireland"
    ],
    "question": "Washington, D.C. is the capital city of which country?",
    "tags": [
      "general_knowledge",
      "capital_cities",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602dc44b176d54800e3cac",
    "correctAnswer": "Glasgow",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Baltimore",
      "Houston",
      "Minneapolis-St Paul"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these cities is in United Kingdom?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "europe",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "623740bdcb85f7ce9e949d1d",
    "correctAnswer": "India",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Thailand",
      "Solomon Islands",
      "Oman"
    ],
    "question": "New Delhi is the capital city of which country?",
    "tags": [
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602d474b176d54800e3c8c",
    "correctAnswer": "Moscow",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "ZÃ¼rich",
      "Barcelona",
      "Rotterdam"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these cities is in Russia?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "europe",
      "russia",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "623b5854fd6c701a921183b1",
    "correctAnswer": "Scotland",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "USA",
      "Russia",
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "question": "In which country would you find the city of Edinburgh?",
    "tags": [
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "625e9dff796f721e95543f38",
    "correctAnswer": "Brazil",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jamaica",
      "Faroe Islands",
      "Iran"
    ],
    "question": "Which country's flag can be described as 'Green with a yellow diamond in the center with a blue celestial globe.'?",
    "tags": [
      "flags",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602dcb014f58b5fc1a3fc5",
    "correctAnswer": "New Zealand",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Australia",
      "Ireland",
      "Canada"
    ],
    "question": "In which country is the city of Auckland?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602e0d4b176d54800e3cbe",
    "correctAnswer": "Colombia",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dominican Republic",
      "Brazil",
      "Ecuador"
    ],
    "question": "In which country is the city of BogotÃ¡?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "6233844362eaad73716a8bf9",
    "correctAnswer": "Lisbon",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Madrid",
      "Sarajevo",
      "Brussels"
    ],
    "question": "What Is The Most Westerly Capital City In Mainland Europe?",
    "tags": [
      "capital_cities",
      "europe",
      "records",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602d334b176d54800e3c86",
    "correctAnswer": "Amsterdam",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rome",
      "DÃ¼sseldorf",
      "ZÃ¼rich"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these cities is in Netherlands?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "europe",
      "general_knowledge",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "6237406fcb85f7ce9e949cfe",
    "correctAnswer": "Paris",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Marseilles",
      "Bordeaux",
      "Monaco"
    ],
    "question": "What is the capital city of France?",
    "tags": [
      "general_knowledge",
      "capital_cities",
      "france",
      "europe",
      "cities",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950a24",
    "correctAnswer": "Spain",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Morocco",
      "Andorra",
      "France"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Portugal?",
    "tags": [
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602d774b176d54800e3c9a",
    "correctAnswer": "Finland",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Italy",
      "Spain",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "question": "Where would you find the city of Helsinki?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "europe",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602dab957e77cecfa4ec32",
    "correctAnswer": "Mumbai",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sydney",
      "Taipei",
      "Yokohama"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these cities is in India?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "asia",
      "india",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "625e9e30796f721e95543f45",
    "correctAnswer": "Red with five yellow stars in the top left.",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Blue with a yellow cross extending to the edges.",
      "Red with a black two headed eagle in the center.",
      "Green, with large white script and a sword."
    ],
    "question": "What does the flag of China look like?",
    "tags": [
      "flags",
      "china",
      "asia",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602d254b176d54800e3c82",
    "correctAnswer": "China",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mongolia",
      "India",
      "Australia"
    ],
    "question": "Where would you find the city of Beijing?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "general_knowledge",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602d584b176d54800e3c91",
    "correctAnswer": "Italy",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Iceland",
      "Finland",
      "Slovakia"
    ],
    "question": "In which country is the city of Rome?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "europe",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9503d7",
    "correctAnswer": "Decimate",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Havoc",
      "Mutilate",
      "Annihilate"
    ],
    "question": "What Name Was Given To The Practise Of Killing Every Tenth Man In A Mutinous Roman Cohort?",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "romans",
      "general_knowledge",
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95031c",
    "correctAnswer": "Boudica",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Joan of Arc",
      "Zenobia",
      "Fulvia"
    ],
    "question": "Who Was the Queen Of The Iceni Tribe Of England Who Led An Uprising Against The Romans?",
    "tags": [
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95032f",
    "correctAnswer": "George Washington",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "John Adams",
      "Abraham Lincoln",
      "Thomas Jefferson"
    ],
    "question": "Who Was The First President Of The United States?",
    "tags": [
      "usa",
      "presidents",
      "people",
      "general_knowledge",
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951908",
    "correctAnswer": "Vesuvius",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Etna",
      "Krakatoa",
      "Pelee"
    ],
    "question": "What volcano destroyed Pompeii?",
    "tags": [
      "italy",
      "volcanoes",
      "the_ancient_world",
      "romans",
      "natural_disasters",
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f9517fa",
    "correctAnswer": "Pompeii",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Genoa",
      "Capua",
      "Ostia"
    ],
    "question": "Which Roman city was buried under volcanic ash from Mount Vesuvius In 79A.D.?",
    "tags": [
      "romans",
      "volcanoes",
      "italy",
      "classics",
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951919",
    "correctAnswer": "Writing a diary about her hide from the Germans in WW2",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Winning a nobel prize for her research into radioactivity",
      "Being the first woman to be elected to a head of state position",
      "Being the first woman in space"
    ],
    "question": "What was Anne Frank famous for?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951863",
    "correctAnswer": "Boston Tea Party",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Houston Tea Party",
      "Atlanta Tea Party",
      "New York Tea Party"
    ],
    "question": "What famous tea party took place in 1773?",
    "tags": [
      "usa",
      "revolutions",
      "wars",
      "1700's",
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f9c4",
    "correctAnswer": "William J. Clinton",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rutherford B. Hayes",
      "Woodrow Wilson",
      "Dwight Eisenhower"
    ],
    "question": "Who was the 42nd president of the USA, in term during the period 1993â2001?",
    "tags": [
      "usa",
      "presidents",
      "1990's",
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f9c0",
    "correctAnswer": "Donald J. Trump",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Benjamin Harrison",
      "George W. Bush",
      "James Monroe "
    ],
    "question": "Who was the 45th president of the USA, in term during the period 2017â2021?",
    "tags": [
      "leaders",
      "presidents",
      "usa",
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951895",
    "correctAnswer": "The League of Nations",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "G8",
      "The Commonwealth of Nations",
      "The Country Club"
    ],
    "question": "What was the predecessor to the United Nations?",
    "tags": [
      "politics",
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f9518d6",
    "correctAnswer": "The Prohibition",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Dry Spell",
      "The Dark Days",
      "The Moonshine"
    ],
    "question": "What Name Was Given To The Period From 1919 To 1933 When Alcohol Was Banned In The USA?",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "1920's",
      "usa",
      "drink",
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f9518c4",
    "correctAnswer": "Enigma",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mystery",
      "Paradox",
      "Riddle"
    ],
    "question": "What Was The Name Given To The Coding Machine Used By The Germans In World War II?",
    "tags": [
      "technology",
      "world_war_2",
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "62611fe54b176d54800e3d78",
    "correctAnswer": "1945",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1921",
      "1880",
      "1972"
    ],
    "question": "When did Alan Turing break the Enigma code?",
    "tags": [
      "events",
      "technology",
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951abd",
    "correctAnswer": "The Titanic",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Majestic",
      "The Enormous",
      "The Colossus"
    ],
    "question": "Which British Liner Sank On Its Maiden Voyage In 1912?",
    "tags": [
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951a08",
    "correctAnswer": "Holocaust",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Auchterarder",
      "Blitzkrieg",
      "Luftwaffe"
    ],
    "question": "Which word describes the Nazi genocide of Jews?",
    "tags": [
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9503ba",
    "correctAnswer": "Babylon",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Atlantis",
      "Jerusalem",
      "Scythia"
    ],
    "question": "Where were the Hanging Gardens?",
    "tags": [
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f9c1",
    "correctAnswer": "Barack Obama",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Calvin Coolidge",
      "Ronald Reagan",
      "Zachary Taylor"
    ],
    "question": "Who was the 44th president of the USA, in term during the period 2009â2017?",
    "tags": [
      "general_knowledge",
      "usa",
      "presidents",
      "people",
      "leaders",
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951c85",
    "correctAnswer": "Watergate",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hotelgate",
      "Croneygate",
      "Corruptiongate"
    ],
    "question": "What was the name of the scandal that forced President Nixon to resign?",
    "tags": [
      "events",
      "presidents",
      "usa",
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f95177f",
    "correctAnswer": "The Mongols",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Huns",
      "The Parthians",
      "The Greeks"
    ],
    "question": "Which people were led by Genghis Khan?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f9eb",
    "correctAnswer": "George Washington ",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Chester Arthur",
      "Ulysses S. Grant",
      "Millard Fillmore"
    ],
    "question": "Who was the 1st president of the USA, in term during the period 1789â1797?",
    "tags": [
      "presidents",
      "usa",
      "firsts",
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950c44",
    "correctAnswer": "The Beach Boys",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Swans",
      "The Velvet Underground",
      "Aerosmith"
    ],
    "question": "Which American rock band released the song 'Good Vibrations'?",
    "tags": [
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94ff14",
    "correctAnswer": "Madonna",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Eric Clapton",
      "Nicki Minaj",
      "Alanis Morissette"
    ],
    "question": "The iconic song 'Vogue' was a hit by which musician?",
    "tags": [
      "songs",
      "musicians",
      "1980's",
      "general_knowledge",
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fe83",
    "correctAnswer": "Lady Gaga",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hikaru Utada",
      "Drake",
      "Madonna"
    ],
    "question": "Which American singer, songwriter, and actress released the song 'Poker Face'?",
    "tags": [
      "songs",
      "general_knowledge",
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "6266bc1fff2394bd44dedff9",
    "correctAnswer": "Bongo",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lute",
      "Ocarina",
      "Saxophone"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these is a percussion instrument?",
    "tags": [
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b39",
    "correctAnswer": "Jonas Brothers",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Pussycat Dolls",
      "Three 6 Mafia",
      "The Velvet Underground"
    ],
    "question": "Which band includes 'Joe Jonas'?",
    "tags": [
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950dc4",
    "correctAnswer": "The Beatles",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple",
      "Feeder",
      "Uriah Heep"
    ],
    "question": "Which band includes 'John Lennon'?",
    "tags": [
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94ff2d",
    "correctAnswer": "Michael Jackson",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nicki Minaj",
      "Neil Young",
      "Eric Clapton"
    ],
    "question": "Who sung the song 'Smooth Criminal'?",
    "tags": [
      "songs",
      "musicians",
      "general_knowledge",
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fd5a",
    "correctAnswer": "The Fresh Prince",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "DJ Jazzy Jeff",
      "Eminem",
      "Jay Z"
    ],
    "question": "What is Will Smith's Rapper Alter Ego?",
    "tags": [
      "pseudonyms",
      "people",
      "musicians",
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fd6a",
    "correctAnswer": "Michael Jackson",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Elton John",
      "Usher",
      "Kylie Minogue"
    ],
    "question": "Whose Autobiography Was Entitled 'Moonwalk'?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "general_knowledge",
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fe7a",
    "correctAnswer": "Lady Gaga",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hikaru Utada",
      "Drake",
      "Madonna"
    ],
    "question": "Which American singer, songwriter, and actress released the song 'Just Dance'?",
    "tags": [
      "songs",
      "musicians",
      "general_knowledge",
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950cf6",
    "correctAnswer": "The Beatles",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Rolling Stones",
      "Pink Floyd",
      "Led Zeppelin"
    ],
    "question": "The iconic album 'Abbey Road' was released by which band?",
    "tags": [
      "rock_music",
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fe67",
    "correctAnswer": "Britney Spears",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Madonna",
      "Alanis Morissette",
      "Nicki Minaj"
    ],
    "question": "Which American singer, songwriter, dancer and actress released the song '...Baby One More Time'?",
    "tags": [
      "1990's",
      "musicians",
      "songs",
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b7e",
    "correctAnswer": "Destiny's Child",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "MercyMe",
      "Three 6 Mafia",
      "The Velvet Underground"
    ],
    "question": "Which band includes 'BeyoncÃ©'?",
    "tags": [
      "general_knowledge",
      "people",
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b4e",
    "correctAnswer": "Bob Marley and the Wailers",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Red Hot Chili Peppers",
      "Boney M.",
      "Gorillaz"
    ],
    "question": "Which band includes 'Bob Marley'?",
    "tags": [
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950d38",
    "correctAnswer": "The Beatles",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple",
      "Feeder",
      "Uriah Heep"
    ],
    "question": "Which English rock band released the studio album 'Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band'?",
    "tags": [
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950c2a",
    "correctAnswer": "ABBA",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "In Flames",
      "HammerFall",
      "Katatonia"
    ],
    "question": "Which Swedish pop group released the song 'Thank You for the Music'?",
    "tags": [
      "pop_music",
      "general_knowledge",
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fec8",
    "correctAnswer": "BeyoncÃ©",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Madonna",
      "Drake",
      "Nicki Minaj"
    ],
    "question": "Which American singer, actress and record producer released the studio album 'Dangerously in Love'?",
    "tags": [
      "general_knowledge",
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fbb1",
    "correctAnswer": "\"Yo Home to Bel-Air\"",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "\"Bohemian Rhapsody\" by Queen",
      "\"I'll Make a Man Out of You\" by Donny Osmond",
      "\"In da Club\" by 50 Cent"
    ],
    "question": "Which song begins with the lyrics: \"Now this is the story all about how / My life got flipped, turned upside down...\"?",
    "tags": [
      "lyrics",
      "songs",
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fbaf",
    "correctAnswer": "\"Mr. Brightside\" by The Killers",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "\"SpongeBob SquarePants Theme\" by Painty the Pirate",
      "\"Hooked on a Feeling\" by B.J. Thomas",
      "\"Let's Go Crazy\" by Prince and The Revolution"
    ],
    "question": "Which song begins with the lyrics: \"Coming out of my cage / And I've been doing just fine...\"?",
    "tags": [
      "songs",
      "lyrics",
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fba7",
    "correctAnswer": "\"I Will Survive\" by Gloria Gaynor",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "\"All Star\" by Smash Mouth",
      "\"Man! I Feel Like a Woman!\" by Shania Twain",
      "\"You're So Vain\" by Carly Simon"
    ],
    "question": "Which song begins with the lyrics: \"At first I was afraid, I was petrified / Kept thinking I could never live without you by my side...\"?",
    "tags": [
      "songs",
      "lyrics",
      "general_knowledge",
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950551",
    "correctAnswer": "the ancient Egyptians",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "shells and of molluscs",
      "the kidneys and their diseases, a branch of medicine",
      "anesthesia and anesthetics; a branch of medicine"
    ],
    "question": "What is Egyptology the study of?",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c3f7cc59eab6f9523ac",
    "correctAnswer": "Amnesia",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Insomnia",
      "Coma",
      "Kleptomania"
    ],
    "question": "A loss of memory is known as what?",
    "tags": [
      "medicine",
      "words",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950513",
    "correctAnswer": "water",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the age of the Earth",
      "human beings killing other human beings",
      "wonders, or monsters"
    ],
    "question": "What is Hydrology the study of?",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "general_knowledge",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9504f6",
    "correctAnswer": "a book by Leibniz on his theory of monads",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Unidentified flying object phenomena",
      "mammals",
      "a branch of geology that studies sediments"
    ],
    "question": "What is Monadology the study of?",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950fa4",
    "correctAnswer": "Stephen Hawking",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Albert Einstein",
      "Richard Feynman",
      "Charles Darwin"
    ],
    "question": "Who wrote 'A Brief History of Time'?",
    "tags": [
      "physics",
      "people",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950467",
    "correctAnswer": "viruses",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the structure, development, and abnormalities of the teeth",
      "parasites",
      "the therapeutic use of plants"
    ],
    "question": "What is Virology the study of?",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "624333c8cfaae40c12961403",
    "correctAnswer": "An Eaglet",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Lamb",
      "An Eyas",
      "A Calf"
    ],
    "question": "What would you call a baby eagle?",
    "tags": [
      "animals",
      "birds",
      "names",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950542",
    "correctAnswer": "the process of biological evolution",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the eyes",
      "crop circles",
      "butterflies and moths"
    ],
    "question": "What is Evolutionary biology the study of?",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9504fa",
    "correctAnswer": "methods",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "dreams",
      "the therapeutic use of plants",
      "a branch of theology concerned with the final events in the history of the world or of mankind"
    ],
    "question": "What is Methodology the study of?",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950491",
    "correctAnswer": "Semitic cultures",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "plant diseases",
      "hearing; a branch of medicine",
      "life"
    ],
    "question": "What is Semitology the study of?",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f95058a",
    "correctAnswer": "Life",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bell ringing",
      "Rheumatic diseases",
      "Syphilis"
    ],
    "question": "What is biology the study of?",
    "tags": [
      "biology",
      "words",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "6243357dcfaae40c129614ad",
    "correctAnswer": "A Hatchling",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Piglet",
      "A Maggot",
      "A Lamb"
    ],
    "question": "What is the word for a young turtle?",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950477",
    "correctAnswer": "Tibet",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "feces",
      "sleep",
      "dragonflies and damselflies"
    ],
    "question": "What is Tibetology the study of?",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "6243347acfaae40c12961447",
    "correctAnswer": "A Mare",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Hen",
      "A Hembra",
      "A Jill"
    ],
    "question": "A female horse is known as what?",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951048",
    "correctAnswer": "Acidity Or Alkalinity",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Radiation",
      "Wind Speed",
      "Gravity"
    ],
    "question": "What Is PH A Measure Of",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "6242cafdd543524f1b19c901",
    "correctAnswer": "A flock",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A fall",
      "A gang",
      "A yoke"
    ],
    "question": "What is the word for a group of birds?",
    "tags": [
      "birds",
      "words",
      "general_knowledge",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "62433573cfaae40c129614a9",
    "correctAnswer": "A Tadpole",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "An Infant",
      "A Piglet",
      "A Cub"
    ],
    "question": "What is the word for a young toad?",
    "tags": [
      "animals",
      "biology",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c3e7cc59eab6f952338",
    "correctAnswer": "Photosynthesis",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Osmosis",
      "Thesis",
      "Carditis"
    ],
    "question": "By what process do plants manufacture energy?",
    "tags": [
      "biology",
      "plants",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c3e7cc59eab6f9522cb",
    "correctAnswer": "Hydroponics",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Aquonics",
      "Horticulture",
      "Waterculture"
    ],
    "question": "What is the name given to the practice of growing plants in liquids rather than soil?",
    "tags": [
      "plants",
      "science",
      "words"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c3f7cc59eab6f952397",
    "correctAnswer": "Symbiosis",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Parasitism",
      "Syncronicity",
      "Parallelism"
    ],
    "question": "What is the word for a relationship between two different types of organism which live together for their mutual benefit?",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f950fdb",
    "correctAnswer": "Grand Theft Auto",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gear to Advance",
      "Grind Them All!",
      "Go to America"
    ],
    "question": "Which video game series is sometimes referred to as GTA?",
    "tags": [
      "society_and_culture"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95010b",
    "correctAnswer": "Atlantis",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gondwana",
      "Pangea",
      "Europa"
    ],
    "question": "Which ancient continent is said to be submerged?",
    "tags": [
      "society_and_culture"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "626288af4b176d54800e3dae",
    "correctAnswer": "Carlsberg",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Heineken",
      "Fosters",
      "Budweiser"
    ],
    "question": "'Probably the best lager in the world' is a slogan associated with which beer brand?",
    "tags": [
      "business",
      "marketing",
      "drink",
      "society_and_culture"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f9511c9",
    "correctAnswer": "The Sea",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Sky",
      "Wine",
      "Horses"
    ],
    "question": "Poseidon was the Greek god of what?",
    "tags": [
      "mythology",
      "ancient_greece",
      "society_and_culture"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "6266e58cff2394bd44dee007",
    "correctAnswer": "Red",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Yellow",
      "Nine",
      "Black"
    ],
    "question": "In French, what is the meaning of the word 'rouge'?",
    "tags": [
      "language",
      "translations",
      "society_and_culture"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "62628864014f58b5fc1a3fd6",
    "correctAnswer": "There are some things money can't buy",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Everywhere you want to be",
      "Because Change Happens",
      "The World's Local Bank"
    ],
    "question": "What is the marketing slogan of Mastercard?",
    "tags": [
      "business",
      "marketing",
      "society_and_culture"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "6293ec2a7f41d6338b96eedc",
    "correctAnswer": "Dictator of Nazi Germany.",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "One of the pioneers of Quantum mechanics",
      "Roman Emperor who accepted the Christian religion.",
      "Physicist who discovered X-rays."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following describes Adolf Hitler?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "history",
      "society_and_culture"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fced",
    "correctAnswer": "Koreanic",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Afroasiatic",
      "Sino-Tibetan",
      "Turkic"
    ],
    "question": "The language 'Korean' belongs to which language family?",
    "tags": [
      "language",
      "society_and_culture"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "6293ebba7f41d6338b96eebb",
    "correctAnswer": "Chinese philosopher.",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Greek politician",
      "Russian theoretical physicist",
      "Mongolian General"
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following describes Confucius?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "history",
      "society_and_culture",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "6293ebcb7f41d6338b96eec0",
    "correctAnswer": "Scientist who discovered The Theory of Relativity.",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Inventor of the telephone.",
      "38th President of the US.",
      "One of the principal interpreters of Confucianism."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following describes Albert Einstein?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "society_and_culture",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "6293ecb67f41d6338b96ef05",
    "correctAnswer": "38th President of the USA. ",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Developed the world's first vaccine (for smallpox).",
      "Italian explorer who landed in America.",
      "Dictator of Nazi Germany."
    ],
    "question": "Which of the following describes John F. Kennedy?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "history",
      "society_and_culture"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951cba",
    "correctAnswer": "A Partridge In A Pear Tree",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "5 Gold Rings",
      "A Turtle Dove",
      "True Love"
    ],
    "question": "What Did My True Love Give To Me On The \"First\" Day Of Christmas\"?",
    "tags": [
      "christmas",
      "lyrics",
      "society_and_culture"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95012c",
    "correctAnswer": "December",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "September",
      "April",
      "November"
    ],
    "question": "In what month is Christmas observed?",
    "tags": [
      "christmas",
      "general_knowledge",
      "society_and_culture"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95012a",
    "correctAnswer": "Olympus",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sinai",
      "Everest",
      "Marathon"
    ],
    "question": "Which Greek mountain was known as the home of the gods?",
    "tags": [
      "mythology",
      "ancient_greece",
      "classics",
      "general_knowledge",
      "society_and_culture"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fce8",
    "correctAnswer": "Indo-European",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "NigerâCongo",
      "Afroasiatic",
      "Dravidian"
    ],
    "question": "The language 'German' belongs to which language family?",
    "tags": [
      "germany",
      "language",
      "society_and_culture"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "626288864b176d54800e3da3",
    "correctAnswer": "Snap! Crackle! Pop!",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Eat Mor Chikin",
      "A glass and a half in every half pound",
      "Melts in your mouth, not in your hands."
    ],
    "question": "What is the marketing slogan of Rice Krispies?",
    "tags": [
      "business",
      "marketing",
      "food",
      "society_and_culture"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951880",
    "correctAnswer": "Davey Jones's Locker",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mark Jacob's Locker",
      "Bootstrap Bill's Locker",
      "Harry Logan's Locker"
    ],
    "question": "What's the resting place of those buried at sea? ",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "general_knowledge",
      "society_and_culture"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "6262880c4b176d54800e3d84",
    "correctAnswer": "Nike",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Reebok",
      "Adidas",
      "Puma"
    ],
    "question": "Which brand is associated with the marketing slogan 'Just do it'?",
    "tags": [
      "business",
      "marketing",
      "society_and_culture"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fcb7",
    "correctAnswer": "Indo-European",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sino-Tibetan",
      "Turkic",
      "NigerâCongo"
    ],
    "question": "The language 'Greek' belongs to which language family?",
    "tags": [
      "language",
      "society_and_culture"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950120",
    "correctAnswer": "Allah",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mohammed",
      "Yaweh",
      "Jehovah"
    ],
    "question": "What is God called in the Muslim faith?",
    "tags": [
      "religion",
      "islam",
      "society_and_culture"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f9510be",
    "correctAnswer": "Six",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Four",
      "Eight",
      "Two"
    ],
    "question": "How many pockets does a snooker table have?",
    "tags": [
      "general_knowledge",
      "numbers",
      "sport"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950027",
    "correctAnswer": "Golf",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tennis",
      "Cricket",
      "Rugby"
    ],
    "question": "With what sport is Jack Nicklaus associated?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "general_knowledge",
      "sport"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f8b7",
    "correctAnswer": "Football",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Athletics",
      "Motor racing",
      "Basketball"
    ],
    "question": "With which sport is Pele associated?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "general_knowledge",
      "sport"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f8ca",
    "correctAnswer": "Athletics",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Snooker",
      "Motor racing",
      "Ice Hockey"
    ],
    "question": "With which sport is Usain Bolt associated?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "general_knowledge",
      "sport"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f896",
    "correctAnswer": "Motor racing",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hockey",
      "Track and field",
      "Table tennis"
    ],
    "question": "With which sport is Michael Schumacher associated?",
    "tags": [
      "general_knowledge",
      "people",
      "sport"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f8ab",
    "correctAnswer": "Basketball",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gymnastics",
      "Rowing",
      "Volleyball"
    ],
    "question": "With which sport is Michael Jordan associated?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "general_knowledge",
      "sport"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950083",
    "correctAnswer": "Basketball",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Volleyball",
      "Football",
      "Baseball"
    ],
    "question": "What Sport Do The Harlem Globetrotters Play?",
    "tags": [
      "sport"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f891",
    "correctAnswer": "Football",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hockey",
      "Tennis",
      "Surfing"
    ],
    "question": "With which sport is David Beckham associated?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "general_knowledge",
      "sport"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f950023",
    "correctAnswer": "Boxing",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rugby",
      "Cricket",
      "Football"
    ],
    "question": "With which sport is Muhammad Ali associated?",
    "tags": [
      "sport",
      "people",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f8a0",
    "correctAnswer": "Boxing",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cricket",
      "Rugby Union",
      "Ice Hockey"
    ],
    "question": "With which sport is Manny Pacquiao associated?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "general_knowledge",
      "sport"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f8c9",
    "correctAnswer": "Tennis",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Football",
      "Table tennis",
      "Motor Racing"
    ],
    "question": "With which sport is Serena Williams associated?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "general_knowledge",
      "sport"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9500a1",
    "correctAnswer": "Ice Hockey",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "American Football",
      "Basketball",
      "Tennis"
    ],
    "question": "In which sport is the Canadian Wayne Gretzky an all time great?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "sport",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f86e",
    "correctAnswer": "Football",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Snooker",
      "Cricket",
      "Motor racing"
    ],
    "question": "With which sport is Cristiano Ronaldo associated?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "general_knowledge",
      "sport"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f8be",
    "correctAnswer": "Tennis",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Badminton",
      "Swimming",
      "Cycling"
    ],
    "question": "With which sport is Roger Federer associated?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "general_knowledge",
      "sport"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f950021",
    "correctAnswer": "Soccer",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Basketball",
      "Volleyball",
      "Rugby"
    ],
    "question": "With which sport is PelÃ© associated?",
    "tags": [
      "sport",
      "people",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f89d",
    "correctAnswer": "Cricket",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Volleyball",
      "Badminton",
      "Ice Hockey"
    ],
    "question": "With which sport is Shane Warne associated?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "sport"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f88d",
    "correctAnswer": "Golf",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Figure skating",
      "Football",
      "Volleyball"
    ],
    "question": "With which sport is Jack Nicklaus associated?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "general_knowledge",
      "sport"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "62417d5a0f96c4efe8d773be",
    "correctAnswer": "New York Yankees",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "New York Cardinals",
      "New York Jets",
      "New York Raiders"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these is a baseball team based in New York?",
    "tags": [
      "sport"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f875",
    "correctAnswer": "Tennis",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gymnastics",
      "Cycling",
      "Swimming"
    ],
    "question": "With which sport is Rafael Nadal associated?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "general_knowledge",
      "sport"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "62c92076a218dd4dc1ca17da",
    "correctAnswer": "Love",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Egg",
      "Zilch",
      "Nil"
    ],
    "question": "What word is used for a score of 0 in a game of tennis?",
    "tags": [
      "sport",
      "tennis",
      "words"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  }

]